<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Jobs>
  <Job jid="2008172" reference="2028816" datePosted="2015-06-24" dateUpdated="2015-06-23T21:41:54Z">
    <Title>Senior Account Executive</Title>
    <Summary>Award-winning, highly regarded PR and Marketing ​agency looking for AE to work across brands in a broad range of sectors.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> <br> Award-winning, highly regarded PR and Marketing&nbsp;&#8203;agency working with brands across the&nbsp;technology, consumer lifestyle, financial services, resource, &#8203;sustainability and not-for-profit sectors.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> <br> &nbsp;&#8203;As a strong Account Executive or Senior Account Executive, &#8203;you bring 12+ months experience working in an agency environment. This role needs someone who will hit the ground running, driving media relationships with new and existing contacts and bring the capability to support integrated campaigns across consumer lifestyle, retail, food and drink and lifestyle &amp; leisure.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> &#8203;<br> Are confident in working with a diverse media set, have solid &#8203;interpersonal &amp; writing skills and a good&#8203; working&#8203;&nbsp;knowledge of&nbsp;&#8203;supporting &#8203;traditional and social media&nbsp;campaigns.&#8203;&nbsp;You will ask questions, be hungry to learn new skills and ideally have grown an established network of local media contacts&#8203;. &#8203;<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Sally Thompson - sally@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Senior Account Executive</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636767" id="4294">PR - Account Executive</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2008181" reference="2028735" datePosted="2015-06-24" dateUpdated="2015-06-23T21:44:28Z">
    <Title>Account Director</Title>
    <Summary>Award-winning​ and​ highly regarded PR and Marketing​ ​Agency with a diverse client set​ spanning across multiple sector</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> Award-winning&#8203; and&#8203;&nbsp;highly regarded PR and Marketing&#8203; &#8203;Agency with a diverse client set&#8203; spanning&#8203;&nbsp;&#8203;across&nbsp;technology, consumer lifestyle, financial services,&nbsp;&#8203;food &amp; drink, &#8203;resource&nbsp;&#8203;and&#8203; sustainability and not-for-profit sectors.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> &#8203;Opportunity to lead a growing team across &#8203;some of the agency's biggest Clients. This role is seeking an Account Director who shows strength in driving client relationships, fostering professional growth and someone who is confident driving new and organic business opportunities. Experience working in consumer technology or enterprise technology would be an advantage but strong experience across sectors will be considered.&nbsp;<br> &nbsp;<br> The agency looks to hire based on culture and experience - the right Client portfolio will be built around an outstanding consultant.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> Will have 6+ years experience in Communications, operating at a senior level that would see you confidently driving&nbsp;existing&nbsp;business &#8203;and become the 'go to' counsel for your team and Clients.&nbsp;<br> &nbsp;<br> You have experience in driving creative and compelling integrated campaigns and are looking for the next step in your career. This is an exciting time to be joining a business that is enjoying recent new business and award wins.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Sally Thompson - sally@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Account Director</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636766" id="4293">PR - Account Director</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2008200" reference="1996818" datePosted="2015-06-24" dateUpdated="2015-06-24T00:00:04Z">
    <Title>Lead Systems Analyst</Title>
    <Summary>Offering an attractive re-location and visa package to London join the "Law firm of the year" two years in a row as their lead systems analyst!</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> Voted "Law firm of the year" two years in a row due to their innovative approach to client services and talent development. Considered a principle partner of the vendor the lead systems analyst will be part of the cutting edge development and innovations of the practice management system solution as a whole as well its application within the firm<br> <br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> <em><span style="text-decoration:underline"><br> Offering an attractive relocation and visa package to&nbsp;<strong>London</strong>&nbsp;the role will see you...</span></em><br> <ul> <li>Analysing and implementing technical changes to practice management systems</li> <li>Providing the technical management and support of all practice management systems&nbsp;</li> <li>Collaborating with members of the IT and Finance teams</li> <li>Managing, maintaining and holding technical ownership of all practice management systems and their related customisations and integrations</li> <li>Fully responsible of escalated 3rd line support calls for all practice management systems</li> </ul> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> <ul> <li>Will be MCSE certified (other Microsoft certification)</li> <li>ITIL Foundation Certificate</li> <li>Will have strong interpersonal and customer service skills</li> <li>Will be a straight shooter who is confident, assertive and able to take ownership</li> <li>Will have first rate communication skills with both technical and non-technical people and proven experience delivering against client objectives</li> <li>Will be have proven analytical and problem solving abilities</li> <li>Will have a strong understanding of database structures, warehouses, theories, principles and practices</li> </ul> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Rob Fanshawe - rob@jobadder.com<br> </em><em> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Lead Systems Analyst</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636748" id="5377">Technology</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636809" id="19">Europe</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636810" id="171">London</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816801" id="613">London</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2012015" reference="2002494" datePosted="2015-06-26" dateUpdated="2015-06-25T23:11:30Z">
    <Title>Country Manager/ Head of Sales- Web/ Social Analytics</Title>
    <Summary>Our client is a leading digital/ social media Saas company with offices around the world</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> Our client is a leading digital/ social media Saas company with offices around the world.<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> - Establish and maintain key strategic client and partner relationships<br> - Present to potential large brands and agencies<br> - Driving sales and effectively managing existing clients&nbsp;<br> - Research and identify key partnership opportunities<br> - Provide management with market feedback<br> - Support senior management in augmenting sales strategies and targets<br> - Build and Manage a team of business developers<br> - Full responsibility on the day-to-day operations of the office as well as P&amp;L<br> <br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> - Bachelor's degree or above in a related field<br> - Minimum of 10 years' relevant experience<br> - Self-starter and motivated multi-tasker with an entrepreneurial spirit<br> - Good knowledge of the social media industry<br> - Experience in working with CRM tools<br> - Possesses a helpful consultative approach<br> - Excellent communications skills, both written and verbal<br> - Experience in managing a team, both local and remote management<br> - P&amp;L experience<br> - Good negotiation skills while listening to client needs<br> <br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel:&nbsp;Rina Lee Zia Zia -&nbsp;R1104286</em><em></em><em></em><em></em><em><br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Country Manager/ Head of Sales- Web/ Social Analytics</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636739" id="5371">Analytics</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2013354" reference="2054030" datePosted="2015-06-29" dateUpdated="2015-06-28T16:49:38Z">
    <Title>Front End Angular Developer</Title>
    <Summary>We are looking for mid-level and experienced Front End Developers who can operate in a fast paced, automomous environment.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[IONIC/ANGULAR Front-end developers, mid and senior levels are urgently needed to join an online business with a dynamic team who are undergoing significant change and who are building a unique and cutting edge platform within the sports industry.<br> <br> Experience required: Strong experience in Angular.<br> <br> We are looking for mid-level and experienced Front End Developers who can operate in a fast paced, automomous environment. You will be used to working in an Agile environment and be excited about working in a start up alongside others who are passionate about being at the forefront of cutting edge projects.<br> <br> Both levels of role will require you to be dedicated to being 'hands on' and will be hired to be a specialist not to be told what to do. Both roles will involve working as part of a small team and liaison with the CTO of the business, bringing your ideas and solutions to the table.<br> <br> Both roles will need someone with experience of working on large scale projects and the candidate for the senior position will have had exposure to all facets of an application not just one, development ops experience, knowledge of servers, managing and configuring, optimising, making educated decisions in reference to architecture applications someone who spots gaps, understands problems and delivers the best solution.<br> <br> <strong>Recent experience with Ionic for mobile. If candidates do not have IONIC they must be strong in Angular. Please note: Candidates who have neither skill as a strength will not be called to discuss this role.<br> </strong><br> Will interview immediately! Please email alice on alice@jobadder.com or call me on 0455578954]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Front End Angular Developer</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636731" id="530">Other</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636781" id="4338">Technical</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2015372" reference="2056261" datePosted="2015-06-30" dateUpdated="2015-06-29T18:09:35Z">
    <Title>Country Manager ANZ</Title>
    <Summary>Leading Global Independent Ad Platform are now looking to build and grow their ANZ team</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong>Company...?</strong><br> <br> A leading Global Independent Ad Platform. Due to huge success they are now looking to build and grow their ANZ team ASAP&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>Role...?</strong><br> <br> This is a rare opportunity for an experienced and well-connected digital advertising sales professional to lead an entire country market, build a team, run and organisation, and earn large uncapped commissions.&nbsp;<br> <br> The Country Manager will lead the Australia and New Zealand markets, reporting to the Director of APAC, who is based in Singapore. The successful executive will be able to operate autonomously at the Sales Director / Managing Director level, in order to build and foster relationships with Publishers and Agency Trading Desks.&nbsp;<br> <ul> <li>Responsible for sourcing, evaluating, closing, and implementing media partnerships</li> <li>Building strong, long lasting relationship with Agency Trading Desks&nbsp;</li> <li>Liaising with the Ad Ops and technology teams to ensure successful delivery of campaigns.</li> <li>Quickly responding to inbound platform leads and enquiries.</li> <li>Manage the sales pipeline in order to maximise revenue while providing accurate and timely forecasts.&nbsp;</li> <li>Tracking and managing sales pipeline and account activities using Salesforce.&nbsp;</li> <li>Demonstrating intense motivation to sell, gain market share and win.&nbsp;</li> <li>Meeting or exceed quarterly revenue targets&nbsp;</li> </ul> <br> <strong>And you...?</strong><br> <br> <ul> <li>Solid background in Digital Sales</li> <li>Experience in digital, display, search, mobile or video advertising</li> <li>Track record of sourcing and closing deals</li> <li>Revenue focused, negotiation and analytical skills across contractual, technical and financial areas</li> <li>Great presentation and communication skills&nbsp;</li> <li>Willingness to work autonomously as a key individual contributor with high comp targets</li> <li>Network of contacts in Publishers, Agencies and Agency Trading Desks is an advantage</li> </ul>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Country Manager / Managing Director / Commercial Director / Sales Director</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636742" id="4270">Digital Sales</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2016297" reference="2071669" datePosted="2015-06-30" dateUpdated="2015-06-29T22:10:56Z">
    <Title>Digital Recruitment Consultant (Sydney)</Title>
    <Summary>Recruiter needed to join our thriving Digital team in Sydney. Trust based flexible culture + great progression opportunities.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-weight:bold">Full Job Description</span><br> </div> <div> <div> <div>Can we change your perception of recruitment? Can you change ours?<br> We are looking for a consultant to join our Digital recruiters in Sydney.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>About Us</strong><br> 33 Talent is an award winning talent acquisition &amp; management services firm specialising in Big Data, Digital and Communications. We provide recruitment, executive search and managed talent consulting services.<br> <br> Our company mission is to positively disrupt the world of recruitment and offer something new to the APAC recruitment market.<br> <br> We strongly urge you to check out more about us and what it's like to work at 33 Talent here! http://www.33talent.com/join-the-team<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> Consultants are responsible for the full 360 degree recruitment process generating revenue from new and existing Digital customers. This incorporates providing superior industry leading service and delivery to candidates and clients, at all times promoting 33 Talent's Mission and Values.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> Success will be measured through achievement of set results, as well as client, candidate, team and manager satisfaction.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>What is Digital?<br> </strong><br> Digital is one of the fastest paced and most exciting sectors to be involved in today and the journey is one that changes and evolves every single day.&nbsp; For us, digital includes digital &amp; social media, mobile, e-commerce and publishing.<br> <br> We work with industry leading figures and brands to monitor trends in the industry and stay up to date with the big opportunities and changes our contacts can take advantage of.&nbsp; The growth of search, mobile, and programmatic marketing are areas we've harnessed for our candidates, and we'll continue to bring them opportunities from emerging specialisms every chance we get.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>And You...&nbsp;</strong><br> We need like-minded people that want to deliver value through excellence in what they do but with a much broader outlook that goes beyond just themselves. We want people who will disrupt the world of recruitment in a positive manner and help continuous progression in both their own development, and with 33 Talent and all those who interact with us.<br> <br> On top of this cultural fit we need someone who:&nbsp;<br> <ul> <li>Is looking for a Consultant or Senior Consultant level role in recruitment</li> <li>Has the desire to manage existing Clients but also the drive to carve out new business opportunities</li> <li>Brings strong commercial acumen / understanding of business</li> <li>Offer strong relationship management skills</li> <li>Is a problem solver &amp; has issue resolution skills</li> <li>Ideally would have previous PR or Digital recruitment experience; however our strong network &amp; reputation will support training &amp; development in this sector</li> </ul> </div> </div> </div>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Digital Recruitment Consultant | Sydney</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636090" id="529">HR &amp; Recruitment</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="817904" id="4323">Recruitment Consultant</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2016321" reference="2071679" datePosted="2015-06-30" dateUpdated="2015-06-29T22:23:04Z">
    <Title>Programmatic Sales Manager</Title>
    <Summary>Sales Manager required by the International leaders in the DMP space. Company offers cutting edge solutions in programmatic &amp; big data</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<div><strong>Programmatic Sales Manager</strong></div> <div>&nbsp;</div> <div>Sales Manager required by the International leaders in the DMP space. Company offers cutting edge solutions in programmatic &amp; big data</div> <div> <div> <div><strong>The Company...</strong><strong><br> </strong><br> Sales Manager required by the global leaders in the DMP space. This company offer cutting edge solutions in programmatic and big data and due to huge success they are in rapid growth mode<br> <br> <strong>The Role...</strong>&nbsp;<br> <br> We are looking for an experienced Sales Manager with a strong background in digital sales to become part of this growing, dynamic and hugely innovative company.&nbsp;<br> <ul> <li>Will see you building a pipeline of opportunity across the product set</li> <li>Will see you identifying and growing excellent relationships with agencies, trade desks and DSP's</li> <li>Will see you working across multiple stakeholders to drive larger engagement and unlock spending</li> <li>Will see you demonstrating an in-depth understanding of the digital market and where to leverage huge global spends to drive sales</li> </ul> <strong>You...</strong><br> <ul> <li><strong>Will have a strong background in sales within the digital advertising space</strong></li> <li>Will be able to discuss programmatic buying, real time bidding, audience targeting and online media business with various high level stakeholders</li> <li>Will have a proven track record of meeting and exceeding sales targets</li> <li>Will have an established network of contacts within the agency space</li> <li>Will be a fun, lively and energetic person who is excited and passionate to be in the industry</li> </ul> </div> </div> </div>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Programmatic Sales Manager</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636742" id="4270">Digital Sales</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2017465" reference="1844347" datePosted="2015-07-01" dateUpdated="2015-06-30T17:28:53Z">
    <Title>SEO Specialists (mid and senior)</Title>
    <Summary>Agency and client-side roles working for a large independent agency or eCommerce company. Excellent career prospects and $$</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> If you're looking to move client-side or into a larger agency role, you'll be spoilt for choice with these great opportunities. Both located in the Sydney CBD and both offer genuine career growth and competitive $$.&nbsp;<br> <br> <br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> ROLE 1 - You'll be working with Tier 1 clients and you'll learn from some of the best Search talent in the business. If you enjoy leading a team (or would like to step up to a leadership role), have experience managing budgets, have a creative mind and love getting involved with formulating and executing SEO strategy, then I'd like to hear from you.<br> <br> ROLE 2 - eCommerce. A more autonomous and strictly SEO focused role for the moment with the opportunity to grow the role into other areas in digital marketing in the future.<br> <br> <br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> <ul> <li>4+ years hands-on experience in SEO campaign management</li> <li>Passion for developing and executing innovative/creative SEO strategy</li> <li>Proven track record in delivering results</li> <li>Experience leading a team (preferred)</li> <li>Local experience or currently living in Sydney</li> <li>Exposure to eCommerce (preferrable)</li> <li>Strong analytical and problem solving skills</li> <li>Contractors/freelancers welcome to apply</li> </ul> <br> <br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Bronwen Kaspers - bronwen@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>SEO Specialist</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636738" id="4267">Advertising Specialist</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2018448" reference="2072388" datePosted="2015-07-01" dateUpdated="2015-07-01T03:54:47Z">
    <Title>Communications Recruitment Consultant (Sydney)</Title>
    <Summary>Experienced Recruiter needed to join our thriving Comms team in Sydney. Trust based flexible culture + great progression opportunities.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<div>Can we change your perception of recruitment? Can you change ours?</div> <div> <div> <div>We are looking for a consultant to join our Communication recruitment team in Sydney.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>About Us</strong><br> 33 Talent is an award winning talent acquisition &amp; management services firm specialising in Big Data, Digital and Communications. We provide recruitment, executive search and managed talent consulting services.<br> <br> Our company mission is to positively disrupt the world of recruitment and offer something new to the APAC recruitment market.<br> <br> We strongly urge you to check out more about us and what it's like to work at 33 Talent here! http://www.33talent.com/join-the-team<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> <ul> <li>Make at least $30,000 worth of placements each month.&nbsp;</li> <li>You're only as good as the people you know, so you need to be meeting new candidates, building relationships, and staying in touch with the best. &nbsp;</li> <li>Become a business development machine! We have a great variety of clients that you can begin working with from day one, and you'll bring in new roles with them, and with new clients too.&nbsp;</li> <li>Expand our business into a new niche within our 3 core industries. This could be a new location, a new specialism or a new type of client.&nbsp;</li> <li>Share your knowledge with your team members.&nbsp; At senior consultant level the next step is to move up to a team manager role, so one of your goals will be to begin guiding and coaching your more junior colleagues.&nbsp;</li> <li>Provide superior industry leading service and delivery to candidates and clients, at all times promoting 33 Talent's Mission and Values</li> </ul> <br> <strong>And You...<br> </strong><br> If you come from a recruitment role and can meet (and beat!) the above results, we'd love to hear from you. If you're from outside the recruitment industry you could still do well in this role if you have B2B sales experience. Anything less than that, and you probably don't have the experience needed to excel in this role. If you think we're wrong, feel free to apply, and list the achievements you've made that will enable you to meet these results.&nbsp;</div> </div> </div>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Communications / PR Recruitment Consultant - Sydney</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636090" id="529">HR &amp; Recruitment</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="817904" id="4323">Recruitment Consultant</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2022808" reference="2080700" datePosted="2015-07-06" dateUpdated="2015-07-05T13:43:13Z">
    <Title>Account Manager</Title>
    <Summary>This Account Manager role will see you managing day-to-day key account activity and project managing a variety of digital campaigns.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong>About the agency:</strong><br> They are a performance-focused digital marketing agency and consistently deliver strategic, innovative and results driven activity. Due to company growth, they are presently seeking an experienced and talented Account Manager to join the team.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>The Role:</strong><br> Reporting directly to the Head of Strategy, the ideal candidate for this role will have proven experience in managing day-to-day account activity and running of a variety of campaigns. Your main objective is to ensure outstanding client satisfaction across some of our key enterprise clients. In addition, you will have the support of an Account Executive. If you have solid account management and communication skills with a passion for digital, then this is the role for you. The team and work environment is highly positive - they work hard and enjoy themselves along the way. There are excellent career progression opportunities with this rapidly growing team. This is a unique opportunity to work in a full service data-driven digital agency and manage activity across creative production, strategy, media activity &amp; our specialist search offering.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>Key activities:</strong><br> <ul> <li>The creative skills and aptitude to develop and deliver campaigns</li> <li>Managing the rollout of campaigns across multiple online channels and co-ordinating the client and the delivery team</li> <li>Being the main point of contact for their Enterprise clients, answering queries and identifying and resolving any issues</li> <li>Managing production timelines across digital projects (websites, mobile, social media &amp; campaign assets)</li> <li>Coordinating workflow across internal and external parties</li> <li>Tracking and optimising projects both internally and externally with clients</li> </ul> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>And you . . .</strong><br> <ul> <li>2-3 years of experience in an Account Manager role within a digitally focused agency OR a Campaign Manager who is tired of operations and wants to move into an account manager role.</li> <li>Relevant tertiary qualifications and an understanding of cross channel marketing</li> <li>Comprehensive knowledge and experience across digital marketing channels - especially SEM, SEO and Media Buying.</li> <li>Excellent client-facing/relationship building and communication skills</li> <li>A calm and friendly nature</li> <li>Strong problem solving skills</li> <li>The ability to plan and multi-task across projects</li> <li>Solid project and time management skills</li> <li>Strong attention to detail and sense of humour</li> </ul> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>The agency culture:</strong><br> They are a personal, genuine and supportive 'digital family' who REALLY care about each and every member of their talented team. Yes, they're smaller than some other agencies - and that's the way they like it! Their brand is their culture and that's what sets them apart. They don't believe in burning you out either. A typical day with them means you'll leave at 5.30pm - on the dot. To them, a business has to be involving and it has to be fun.<br> <br> <span style="text-decoration:underline">All employees enjoy -</span><br> <ul> <li>Breakfast, fruit and open bar</li> <li>Friday 'beer-pong' competition</li> <li>Weekly 'lunch safari'</li> <li>Beer n' Brains - brainstorming sessions</li> </ul> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Bronwen Kaspers - bronwen@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Account Manager - Digital</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636736" id="4265">Account Manager</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2022922" reference="2080806" datePosted="2015-07-06" dateUpdated="2015-07-05T14:12:23Z">
    <Title>Data Analyst/Trader</Title>
    <Summary>Are you a Trader looking to be involved in setting up a Trading Desk or possibly a Data Analyst/Campaign Manager looking to learn programmatic?</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong>&nbsp;<strong>About the agency:</strong><br> They are a performance-focused digital marketing agency located in Sydney CBD. Due to company growth, they are seeking an experienced and talented Data Analyst/Trader to join the team.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>The Role:</strong><br> Reporting directly to the Head of Strategy, the ideal candidate for this role will have either a minimum 1 year of experience at an agency trading desk or be an "insights'' person who wants to learn programmatic. The role is&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"><strong>NOT JUST</strong>&nbsp;</span>a programmatic role - it also involves audience insights and attribution. The team and work environment is highly positive - they work hard and enjoy themselves along the way. There are excellent career progression opportunities with this rapidly growing team. This is a unique opportunity to work in a full service data-driven digital agency and establish their trading desk.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>Key activities:</strong><br> <ul> <li>Setting up the trading desk (looking at DSP options, potential DMP partnerships, feeding in to Ad Server)</li> <li>Determining the training program for chosen platform</li> <li>Running programmatic campaigns (determining bidding strategies &amp; optimising campaigns)</li> <li>Setting up the attribution platform (they're looking at using CAKE but open to recommendations based on research)</li> <li>Once the attribution platform chosen, providing insights to feed into strategy work</li> <li>Set up reporting platform (cross channel dashboard that they've just signed with)</li> <li>Feeding data points in to platform and ensuring all data is correctly tracking/reporting</li> <li>Being the data lead for the office, so looking at all available data points and pulling interesting and useful insights</li> <li>Role has a lot of autonomy and will be relied on in the office for providing insights and stats that form the basis of key decisions and performance strategies</li> </ul> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>And you . . .</strong><br> <ul> <li>1+ years of experience in a similar role within a digitally focused agency</li> <li>Relevant tertiary qualifications</li> <li>A background in performance, campaign management/data analytics</li> <li>Experience using Accuen, MediaMath, AppNexis or DoubleClick etc.</li> <li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills</li> <li>The ability to plan and multi-task across projects</li> <li>Exceptional relationship management skills</li> <li>Solid project and time management skills</li> <li>Strong attention to detail</li> <li>Sense of humour</li> </ul> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>The agency culture</strong><br> They're a personal, genuine and supportive 'digital family' who REALLY care about each and every member of the talented team. Yes, they're smaller than some other agencies - and that's the way they like it! Their brand is their culture and that's what sets them apart. They don't believe in burning you out either. A typical day with this agency means you'll leave at 5.30pm - on the dot. To them, a business has to be involving and it has to be fun. All employees enjoy -<br> <ul> <li>Breakfast, fruit and open bar</li> <li>Friday 'beer-pong' competition</li> <li>Weekly 'lunch safari'</li> <li>Beer n' Brains - brainstorming sessions</li> </ul> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Bronwen Kaspers - bronwen@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Data Analyst/Trader</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636739" id="5371">Analytics</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2025419" reference="2031742" datePosted="2015-07-07" dateUpdated="2015-07-06T19:00:16Z">
    <Title>Data Analyst, Global Analytics Hub</Title>
    <Summary>Looking to further your career in Data Analytics? Join the EDB-STRAT program with Lenovo!</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> Lenovo in conjunction with the EDB is launching a Strategic Attachment and Training (STRAT) Programme to build up key manpower capabilities in Singapore's workforce for emerging sectors and activities. This two-year program will help recent graduates obtain on-job-training while working closely with existing staff on live projects.<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> We are seeking a Data Analyst with experience working for an enterprise multi-national utilizing multi-datasets and sources running predictive, prescriptive and reactive analytics for all channels of the business. Your role is to provide accurate, timely, relevant and quality analysis for a dynamic business.<br> &nbsp;<br> You will be reporting to Senior Analytics Manager / Analytics Manager and offer effective reporting, insight and analysis for multiple stakeholders, internal clients, locations and priorities. You will be working hands-on and delivering flexible solutions ensuring stakeholder satisfaction.<br> <br> <em>Responsibilities:</em><br> <ul> <li>Data Analysis &amp; Research</li> <li>Liaise both internally within the hub as well as externally with business stakeholders for completion of data analysis and reporting.</li> <li>Support the development and testing of hypotheses across all functional data sets supplied by the business</li> <li>Researching and applying multidisciplinary techniques, findings and approaches to provide solutions driving the businesses understanding of its market</li> <li>Implementing and analyzing algorithms that will substantially impact the company's understanding of its data</li> <li>Support the proof of concept, and development of tools and applications</li> <li>Work with the manager to define key questions and projects that will transform the business</li> </ul> *This position will be based in Singapore<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...</strong><br> <ul> <li>Bachelor's degree in Engineering, IT, Math, Statistics, Sciences or technical discipline</li> <li>Candidates will have a maximum 2 years industry experience upon graduation</li> <li>Expert knowledge of R programming; VBA / Shiny App / SAS / SPSS / Tableau experience is desirable;&nbsp;</li> <li>Ability to understand and extract data from large and complex data sets (structured &amp; unstructured)</li> <li>Basic knowledge of data quality measurements, methodology and reporting tools</li> <li>Basic knowledge of data management</li> <li>Basic knowledge of statistical methods and market leading data analysis tools and platforms</li> <li>Strong results driven personality, with a high level of enthusiasm, energy and confidence</li> <li>Excellent analytical, communication, organizational and presentation skills</li> <li>Ability to demonstrate flexibility and integrity: be able and willing to work hands on, independently or with a small team</li> </ul> <br> **Please note that applicants will need to be a Singapore Citizen or PR to be eligble for the STRAT programme. You must also have graduated no more than 2 years ago.**<br> <br> <strong>To apply:</strong>&nbsp;please use the application buttons below, or e-mail your CV in Words format to kay@jobadder.com<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em></em><em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel:&nbsp;Kay Lee Meng Qi -&nbsp;R1546136</em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Data Analyst, Data Analysis</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636091" id="526">Big Data</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636735" id="4264">Data Scientist</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2025430" reference="2080478" datePosted="2015-07-07" dateUpdated="2015-07-06T16:42:01Z">
    <Title>Account Director</Title>
    <Summary>Account Director required by Global leader in the data, analytics and software space. Fast paced &amp; dynamic team with great career growth oppos</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong>The company...<br> </strong><br> <ul> <li>A Global leader in the data, analytics and software space with offices in the US, Europe, and across APAC</li> <li>Offering data and technologies that give clients the power to manage audiences, personalise customer experiences and create profitable relationships.</li> <li>Very cool, funky CBD offices and a fresh, young and dynamic culture.</li> </ul> &nbsp; &nbsp;<br> <strong>The Role...</strong>&nbsp;<br> <br> <ul> <li>Will see you achieving incremental growth targets by leveraging your experience of upselling complex data solutions</li> <li>Will see you proactively identifying new revenue opportunities, driving account growth and increasing cross-sell opportunities</li> <li>Will see utilising your experience in leading, negotiating and renewing multi-million AU$ contracts </li> <li>Will see you driving exceptional levels of client satisfaction and bringing new ideas and solutions to your accounts</li> <li>Will see you as an expert in building and developing strong lasting client relationships, providing regular updates and engaging in extensive communication</li> </ul> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>You...&nbsp;&nbsp; <br> </strong><br> <ul> <li>Must have solid experience in sales/account management in the data and digital marketing space</li> <li>Will have a good understanding of data marketing technologies including; data insights, analytics and CRM</li> <li>Will have a proven track record in meeting and exceeding sales goals involving large and complex deals</li> <li>Will have a passion for building strong relationships with both clients and the wider internal team</li> <li>Will have an outgoing and friendly personality&nbsp;</li> </ul> <strong>Not for you but you know who?&nbsp;</strong><br> If this seems ideal for someone you know please pass it on.]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Account Director / Account Manager / Sales Manager / Senior Account Manager</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636738" id="4267">Advertising Specialist</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2027267" reference="2081743" datePosted="2015-07-08" dateUpdated="2015-07-07T16:48:48Z">
    <Title>Campaign Manager</Title>
    <Summary>Digital Campaign Manager required by award winning global company who are pioneers in the mobile Ad/Tech space</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong>The Company...</strong><br> &nbsp;<br> They are global company who are pioneers in the mobile space, offering intelligent location data to define and target digital audiences.&nbsp; This rapidly growing company are working with cutting technologies and have a unique offering in the Australian market.<strong><br> </strong><br> For this brand new role, based in Sydney, we are looking for a bright, highly organised campaign guru who is passionate about current mobile advertising trends<br> <strong><br> The Role...</strong><br> <br> <br> <ul> <li>Will see you manage a portfolio of campaigns from start to finish, optimizing and developing them to target and budget to insure performance goals are met</li> <li>Will see you use analytics to track and measure campaigns against deliverables to ensure optimal results are achieved</li> <li>Will see you report on campaign performance, providing feedback to internal teams and clients</li> <li>Will see you build strong long term relationships key units across the business</li> <li>Will see you working with some of the most genuine and nicest people in the Australian market</li> </ul> <strong></strong>&nbsp;<br> <strong></strong>&nbsp;<br> <strong>You...?</strong><br> <br> <br> <ul> <li>Will have Digital Campaign Management experience </li> <li>Will have a thorough understanding of advertising metrics: CPM, CPC, CTR, eCPM etc</li> <li>Will have an ability to work with multiple ad serving systems</li> <li>Will have exceptional communication skills and will thoroughly enjoy networking at all levels</li> <li>Will have strong analytical skills and an ability to translate this data</li> </ul> <strong><br> <br> </strong>&nbsp;<br> <strong>How to get in touch...?</strong><br> <br> Hit the Apply Now button to take advantage of this exciting opportunity!<br> Not for you but you know who? Share with your Peers]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Campaign Manager / Campaign Analyst / Operations Executive / Operations Manager</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636738" id="4267">Advertising Specialist</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2030618" reference="2083478" datePosted="2015-07-10" dateUpdated="2015-07-09T16:08:14Z">
    <Title>Digital Producer</Title>
    <Summary>Are you a digital marketer with experience in managing the production of marketing-driven digital assets?</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The role . . .</strong><br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> Our client is a leading Digital Marketing Agency specialising in strategic partnerships with some of Australia's most respected Brands.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> They're looking for a team member to manage the end to end production of marketing-driven digital assets (websites, landing pages, social pages, videos, infographics). This includes mapping the customer journey for clients and providing strategic advice around campaign execution, developing an understanding of each client's target audience and ensuring the message is reflected clearly across all digital platforms, troubleshooting production issues and keeping internal/external teams "in the loop" at all times.<br> <br> You'll need to be passionate about Digital, and have experience in managing creative resources.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> In the role, you'll be working closely with our professional services team, and reporting directly to our Project Manager.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> Do you understand what really matters in Digital? Do you want the chance to drive cutting edge projects? This position is ready to go and will go fast.<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>And you . . .</strong><br> &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <ul> <li>Demonstrated success in <strong>digital marketing</strong> and <strong>production</strong>.</li> <li><strong>** 2+ years agency experience a real plus **</strong></li> <li><strong>High level proficiency in Word, PowerPoint and Excel</strong></li> <li>Dynamic, energetic, pro-active attitude and driven towards communication (staff and client), client outcomes and business growth.</li> <li>Clear, independent and lateral thinker.</li> <li>Flexible and adaptive to growth and change.</li> <li>Enjoy problem-solving, with a strong desire to help (clients and team members).</li> <li>Good listener.</li> <li>Excitement/thirst for learning and growing, regularly devouring knowledge in the Digital space.</li> <li>Passionate about digital marketing.</li> <li>Thrives off autonomy (with support).</li> <li>Enjoy working with internal and outsourced teams and bringing the best out of them.</li> <li>Results-focused.</li> <li>Sense of humour.</li> <li>Strong/clear written and verbal communication skills.</li> </ul> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> <strong>The agency culture:</strong><br> They are a personal, genuine and supportive 'digital family' who REALLY care about each and every member of their talented team. Yes, they're smaller than some other agencies - and that's the way they like it! Their brand is their culture and that's what sets them apart. They don't believe in burning you out either. A typical day with them means you'll leave at 5.30pm - on the dot. To them, a business has to be involving and it has to be fun.<br> <br> <span style="text-decoration:underline">All employees enjoy -</span><br> <ul> <li>Breakfast, fruit and open bar</li> <li>Friday 'beer-pong' competition</li> <li>Weekly 'lunch safari'</li> <li>Beer n' Brains - brainstorming sessions</li> </ul> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Bronwen Kaspers - bronwen@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Digital Producer</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636741" id="4269">Digital Media</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2033570" reference="2083384" datePosted="2015-07-13" dateUpdated="2015-07-12T18:49:37Z">
    <Title>Marketing Manager</Title>
    <Summary>Marketing Manager required for global Internet Media business within the travel sector. Looking for a commercially minded marketing hunter.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong>The Company...</strong><br> <br> <ul> <li>A profitable, high-growth, Internet media business with more than a decade of market leadership in travel deals publishing. Every week, this company engages with millions of subscribers worldwide.&nbsp;</li> <li>With 24 offices around the world, and presence in more than 11 countries this business encourages global careers and employees are encouraged to explore the world.&nbsp;</li> <li>This company is extremely fast-paced and offer excellent, culture rewards and benefits.&nbsp;</li> </ul> <br> <strong>The role...</strong><br> &nbsp;<br> <ul> <li>Will see you identify opportunities to drive membership acquisition in order to meet volume targets and increase CPA</li> <li>Will see you developing strategies for self-funding e-commerce advertising including retargeting, display and targeted partnerships</li> <li>Will see you executing and communicating the social media strategy working closely with the production team and other members of the business</li> <li>Will see you driving the Trade marketing strategy, organising trade shows and updating sales collateral</li> </ul> &nbsp;<br> <strong>You...?</strong><br> &nbsp;<br> <ul> <li>Will be a commercially minded marketing hunter who thrives in a fast paced enivorment</li> <li>Must have a solid background in online marketing, ideally in the travel, hospitality or e-commerce sectors</li> <li>Will be an outgoing, entrepreneurial and energetic person who loves to tackle challenges</li> <li>Strong self-starter with the ability to turn creative ideas into tactical successes</li> <li>Will have excellent verbal and written communication skills.</li> </ul>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Marketing Manager / Marketing Consultant / Digital Marketing Manager</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636763" id="4290">Marketing Manager</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2033684" reference="2046926" datePosted="2015-07-13" dateUpdated="2015-07-12T19:24:29Z">
    <Title>Creative Lead</Title>
    <Summary>Looking for a challenge, be it technologically-driven or an exciting start-up environment? Be part of our client's newest team as a Creative Lead!</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong>The Company...<br> <br> </strong>Our client is a new leading technology and creative company with 10 offices around the world, working with top notch clients in the consumer sector.<br> <br> <strong>The Role...</strong><br> <br> This is a hybrid role sat between the creative, commercial and technology teams. You will be part of the global team working for some of the world's most exciting brands. You will develop an intimate understanding of the capabilities that the our client's products' offer, working with the local team at the forefront of the operations to create and conceive exciting new campaigns.<br> <br> <strong>Responsibilities...</strong><br> <br> From interactive games to unique advertising campaigns; the primary role will be to define, develop and deliver exciting campaigns for clients. In conjunction with commercial teams, you will scope, conceptualise and deliver on the bleeding edge of advertising innovation. You will drive both an artistic vision as well as the ability to hands on create and build each project in which way you see fit. You will of course be given plenty of training but your ability to pick up ideas and run with them will help you hit the ground running.&nbsp;<br> <br> The client is looking for experienced creative professionals that shares their dream of making amazing experiences at the cutting edge of mobile technology.&nbsp;<br> <strong><br> &amp; You..</strong><br> <br> Ideally, you have a portfolio of amazing work and love working in fast paced environments. Also, you will have:<br> <br> &bull; Deep experience of using a range of creative design tools<br> &bull; Understanding of mobile app, mobile advertising and game design<br> &bull; Innovative vision and creative flair combined with an understanding of advertising<br> &bull; A bonus would be a knowledge of front end development skills<br> &bull; Experience with 3D Modelling software would be a benefit<br> &bull; A passion for making amazing things<br> &bull; Fluency in English is required to be successful in this international environment<br> &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> &nbsp;<strong>To apply:</strong>&nbsp;please use the application buttons below, or e-mail your portfolio link and<br> &nbsp;CV in Words format to kay@jobadder.com<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and numerous other corporate, agency and network clients. &nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to hello@jobadder.com &nbsp;We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> </em><em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel:&nbsp;Kay Lee Meng Qi -&nbsp;R1546136</em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Art director, Creative Lead, senior art designer, digital, mobile, creative</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636740" id="4268">Creative</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2034424" reference="2054031" datePosted="2015-07-13" dateUpdated="2015-07-13T01:24:42Z">
    <Title>Senior Lead Developer (PHP)</Title>
    <Summary>Join an online business who are building a unique and cutting edge platform within the sports industry.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> <br> Senior Lead Developer (PHP) is urgently needed to join an online business with a dynamic team who are undergoing significant change and who are building a unique and cutting edge platform within the sports industry.<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> <br> Be hired to be a specialist not to be told what to do. This role will involve working as part of a small team and liaison with the CTO of the business, bringing your ideas and solutions to the table.<br> <br> <strong>And You</strong><br> <ul> <li>We are looking for an experienced PHP Developer who can operate in a fast paced, autonomous environment. You will be used to working in an Agile environment and be excited about working in a start up alongside others who are passionate about being at the forefront of cutting edge projects.</li> <li>5 years recently dedicated PHP Programming experience</li> <li>You will be dedicated to being 'hands on' but also have the experience behind you whereby you can see the overall picture.</li> <li>80%/20% split between programming and architecture work</li> <li>Laravel PHP Framework experience and knowledge is strongly desired. Experience of Symfony would be of interest, but candidates who have Laravel will be interviewed as a priority.</li> <li>Experience of working on large scale projects and have had exposure to all facets of an application not just one, development ops experience, knowledge of servers, managing and configuring PHP, optimising, making educated decisions in reference to architecture applications someone who spots gaps, understands problems and delivers the best solution.</li> </ul> Will interview immediately! Please email alice on alice@jobadder.com or call me on 0455578954<br> <br> <br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Alice Silver - alice@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Senior Lead Developer (PHP)</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636731" id="530">Other</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636781" id="4338">Technical</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2036505" reference="2085181" datePosted="2015-07-14" dateUpdated="2015-07-14T02:50:24Z">
    <Title>Digital Strategy Director (Agency)</Title>
    <Summary>Experienced Digital Strategy Lead / Director needed at this world renowned PR &amp; Communications Agency</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong>The Company...</strong><br> A world-leading PR &amp; Communications agency with a strong reputation, excellent client roster and a leading record in Digital.<br> <br> <br> <strong>The Role...</strong><br> This role oversees <strong>strategy planning for digital &amp; integrated</strong> campaigns in Singapore, working into social/digital for the region. You'll collaborate with team leaders to identify and sell digital/integrated solutions.<br> <br> Working with clients from different sectors (e.g. Tech to FMCG),&nbsp;you know how to extract actionable digital plans from consumer research &amp; insights. You'll also support learning &amp; development internally, from training juniors to conducting agency-wide sharing sessions.<br> <br> <br> <strong>...&amp; You</strong><br> <ul> <li>10 years+ working in digital marketing / communications</li> <li>5 years experience leading digital/social teams or projects</li> <li>Ability to interpret quali/quantitative research</li> <li>Familiar with digital platforms &amp; solutions (social, listening, paid, SEO)</li> <li>Understanding of tech delivery systems is advantageous (programming)</li> </ul> <strong><br> Apply Now</strong><br> Hit the Apply Now buttons or send your CV in Word format to riley@jobadder.com<br> <br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients. &nbsp;Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298</em><br> <em>EA Personnel Riley Kim -&nbsp;R1328361</em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Experienced Digital Strategist needed at this world renowned PR Agency</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636736" id="4265">Account Manager</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2038110" reference="2084941" datePosted="2015-07-15" dateUpdated="2015-07-14T21:27:09Z">
    <Title>Account Director</Title>
    <Summary>Well respected Sydney based PR agency known for its entrepreneurial spirit and industry accolades across PR, Social and Experiential.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> A well respected Sydney based PR agency with a close knit team. Known for its&nbsp;entrepreneurial&nbsp;spirit and industry accolades&nbsp;across PR, Social and Experiential.&nbsp;<br> <br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> An exciting opportunity exists for an ambitious, motivated and accountable Account Director looking for the opportunity to work across multiple sectors and expand their&nbsp;strategic, leadership and communications skills.<br> This role would see the right Consultant independently driving Client relations, supporting team development &amp; growth and becoming an integral part of the decision making within the business. A 2iC role to the Managing Director - lots of opportunity for growth in a supportive and consultative environment.&nbsp;<br> Client sectors include consumer health, travel &amp; lifestyle, food &amp; drink, business &amp; technology<br> <br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> Are an all rounder - you have a creative mind and a passion for driving integrated campaigns. You are either a Senior Account Manager ready for a step up into a more senior role or an Account Director looking for greater autonomy. You are ready for Client direction, have the confidence to create and execute insightful PR strategy, integrate communications across disciplines and the&nbsp;desire to motivate &amp; inspire your team &amp; Clients.&nbsp;<br> <br> 6+ years PR experience a must. Consultants with local industry experience preferred.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Pty Ltd</em><br> <em>Recruiter: Sally Thompson - sally@jobadder.com<br> </em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Account Director / Agency 2iC</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636766" id="4293">PR - Account Director</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2039986" reference="1959035" datePosted="2015-07-16" dateUpdated="2015-07-15T21:57:06Z">
    <Title>Social Metrics and Analytics Assistant</Title>
    <Summary>Looking to build your career foundation in social media analytics space? Join the LENOVO-EDB STRAT programme!</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Role</strong><br> Lenovo in conjunction with the EDB is launching a Strategic Attachment and Training (STRAT) Programme to build up key manpower capabilities in Singapore's workforce for emerging sectors and activities. This two-year program will help recent graduates obtain on-job-training while working closely with existing staff on live projects.<br> <br> <em>Responsibilities</em><br> <ol> <li>Work with the metrics and analytics teams to provide the detailed reports about the reach of social media internally and externally at Lenovo</li> <li>Work with the manager and the Social Technologist in maintaining a best in class approach to selecting the most appropriate tools to help facilitate Social Media metrics, data and insights</li> <li>Assist in providing campaign analytics</li> <ul> <li>Developing key performance indicators relevant to the campaign objectives</li> <li>Setting out the methodology for tracking and the process for tracking</li> <li>Dashboard creation using current suite of tools (i.e. Sprinklr)</li> <li>Tracking of results throughout campaigns</li> <li>Post campaign reporting</li> </ul> <li>Support for the manager in developing social media targets at a WW and country level</li> <li>Ongoing monitoring of performance against targets and work with manager to provide insights to markets against their performance</li> <li>Content analysis and insights at a WW and country level</li> <li>Contribute to integration of Lenovo dot com and Social properties utilising existing tools (i.e. awe.sm) and working with Social Technologist in assessing all potential analytics tools</li> <li>Assist in providing analytics against the Lenovo INsiders Advocacy programme</li> <li>Assist in the development and reporting of monthly/quarterly Executive reports on Social Media performance</li> <li>Maintenance and administration of WW Social Media dashboard (Socialbakers) ensuring data is both accurate and 'clean'</li> <li>Assist in the development and maintenance of the Social Health Index</li> <li>Provide ad hoc reports on Social Media metrics across the organisation</li> <li>Develop a strong relationship with the Global Analytics Hub and the Social Listening team</li> <li>Look for opportunities to post, partner or participate in social media on behalf of Lenovo</li> </ol> *This position will be based in Singapore<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> <ol> <li>Experience with Omniture, Google Analytics, WebTrends, Radian6, Sprinklr or relevant internet statistical gathering tools</li> <li>Working knowledge of statistical analysis, probability and corresponding visualization tools/methods</li> <li>Understanding of reach, lift, engagement, and interaction metric analysis w/ regards to FOAF (Friend-of-a-friend) and/or social media calculation issues.</li> <li>Strong statistical analysis background</li> <li>Understanding of ontology, information sciences, and library sciences</li> <li>Ability to work independently and with initiative</li> <li>Excellent English comprehension and writing skills and extreme tact in interpersonal dealings</li> <li>Willingness to flex hours to overlap some US hours&nbsp;</li> </ol> &nbsp;<br> **Please note that applicants will need to be a Singapore Citizen or PR to be eligble for the STRAT programme. You must also have graduated no more than 2 years ago.**<br> <em></em>&nbsp;<br> <em>Nice to haves</em><br> <ol> <li>Experience with development/construction of statistical and sampling algorithms for reporting</li> <li>Database and/or Data-warehousing experience</li> <li>Experience in social media API scripting and development</li> <li>Experience working in an international organization&nbsp;</li> </ol> <strong>To apply:</strong>&nbsp;please use the application buttons below, or e-mail your CV in Words format to kay@jobadder.com<br> <br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em></em><em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel:&nbsp;Kay Lee Meng Qi -&nbsp;R1546136</em><br> <em><br> </em><em> </em><em> </em><em></em><em></em><em></em><em> </em><em></em><em></em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Social Metrics and Analytics Assistant - Graduate STRAT Program</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636739" id="5371">Analytics</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2043704" reference="2047893" datePosted="2015-07-20" dateUpdated="2015-07-19T19:25:58Z">
    <Title>Managing Director - PR Agency</Title>
    <Summary>Global boutique require an MD to manage the successful Singapore office.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> A PR agency often described as a "Global Boutique" has an office of&nbsp;less than 20, giving it that&nbsp;real independent feel regardless of being part of a group. &nbsp;With&nbsp;a strong tech practice they also focus on consumer practice as well as a growing into healthcare.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> Running the Singapore office requires&nbsp;3 main areas of focus, firstly is client servicing, as well new business and&nbsp;managing an office.&nbsp;<br> Managing the development of talent in Singapore is key part of managing the office. You will be responsible for training &amp; development, recruitment and maintaining the high rate of talent retention.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> Aside from culture fit,&nbsp;success&nbsp;in this role, will relay on you being very hands on, aggressive in pursuit of new business, confident and entrepreneurial. &nbsp;<br> <br> You will have previous experience as an MD or Deputy MD, be from an agency background in a&nbsp;regional role. &nbsp;Ideally a background in tech, consumer or/and healthcare would be beneficial but is not essential.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel: Katie-Jo Green -&nbsp;R1441403<br> </em><em></em><em></em><em></em><em> </em><em></em><em></em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>PR, Communications, comms, Director, Manager, Tech, Healthcare, Consumer</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636772" id="4299">PR Manager</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2043707" reference="2022151" datePosted="2015-07-20" dateUpdated="2015-07-19T19:26:45Z">
    <Title>Consumer Insights Director</Title>
    <Summary>A global Communications company looking for an experienced and well-connected opinion research specialist to support the firm's offer in SEast Asia.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company<br> </strong><br> This global communications firm was founded in the mid 80's. &nbsp;The office in Singapore is young but quickly growing and are now looking for an experienced and well-connected opinion research specialist to support the firm's offer in South East Asia.<br> <br> <strong>The Role<br> </strong><br> The successful candidate will join a growing team of 10+ strategic communications specialists based in Singapore with a special focus on providing primary research and analytics solutions to inform, guide and measure the impact of the businesses communications activities. The&nbsp;firm's opinion research division which comprises a team of 20+ insight specialists in the US, Europe and Asia<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;<br> </strong><br> The candidate will need to have significant opinion research experience across the South East Asia region, a deep understanding of local business issues and a strong network of contacts in Singapore and elsewhere around the region.&nbsp;<br> -&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>10-15 years' relevant opinion &amp; market research experience<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><br> <span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>-&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>Flexible and able to work across multiple modes of research - quantitative, qualitative and analytics<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><br> <span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>-&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>Deep understanding &amp; experience with local businesses in South East Asia<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><br> <span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>-&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>Strong local network within the business community<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><br> <span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>-&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>Entrepreneurial self-starter<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><br> <span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>-&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>A proven track record for marketing and selling research services<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><span style="text-decoration:underline"></span><br> <span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>-&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span style="text-decoration:underline"></span>Local language capabilities considered an advantage but not essential<br> <br> To find out more, click apply or email your CV and cover letter to careers@jobadder.com!<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel: Katie-Jo Green -&nbsp;R1441403<br> <br> </em><em></em><em></em><em></em><em></em><em></em><em> </em><em></em><em></em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Market Research, Analytic, Insight, Optinions</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636764" id="4291">Marketing Research</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2043712" reference="2056099" datePosted="2015-07-20" dateUpdated="2015-07-19T19:28:53Z">
    <Title>VP - Consumer</Title>
    <Summary>Award winning PR agency are offering you the opportunity to be a key part of their expansion into Asia.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> With over 150 employees across the US and UK as well as a local, regional and global client base, this PR agency are in a ideal position to branch out the Asian market.<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> Part of the regional leadership team, you will be based in Singapore reporting to the MD in Hong Kong. &nbsp;You will be responsible for developing the relationship with the existing global client base in Singapore as well as leveraging off other relationships to build more business locally and regionally.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong><br> To be successful in this role you will need a minimum of 7 years&nbsp;experience&nbsp;in PR, primarily in the consumer industry.&nbsp;<br> Cross cultural experience in SE Asia would be ideal, specifically -&nbsp;Philippines, Indonesia, Malaysia, Japanese or Korean.<br> Looking for good planning and creative pedigree, the ability to translate client briefs into plans and deliver.&nbsp;<br> It is essential to the success of this role that you are entrepreneurial, driven and you can work independently day to day without oversight.&nbsp;<br> <br> Regional&nbsp;travel expect in this role.<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited.</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298.<br> </em><em>EA Personnel: Katie-Jo Green -&nbsp;R1441403.<br> </em><em></em><em></em><em> </em><em></em><em></em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>VP, Consumer, 'Public relations, Comms, Communications, PR</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636772" id="4299">PR Manager</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2043716" reference="1883366" datePosted="2015-07-20" dateUpdated="2015-07-19T22:00:17Z">
    <Title>Senior Communications Manager</Title>
    <Summary>This Asian airline is seeking a Senior Communications Manager to strengthen and protect the company reputation across Asia.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> This international airline, based from its Global HQ in the APAC region, is seeking a Senior Regional Communications Manager&nbsp;to work closely with the Group Head of Corporate Communications in protecting and strengthening company reputation across Asia, particular Japan,&nbsp;Singapore and Hong&nbsp;Kong.&nbsp;<br> <br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> With 3 direct reports and 2 indirect you will be responsible for driving and developing strategic plans.&nbsp; You will oversee and have input to all internal and external communications materials ensuring effective delivery.&nbsp; You will manage the corporate communication budget and&nbsp;act&nbsp;as&nbsp;the spokesperson for the airline.&nbsp;<br> <br> You will provide leadership and performance management for your teams, maintain strong relationships with all internal and external stakeholders whilst strengthening the communications strategy and function.&nbsp;<br> <br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...<br> </strong><br> It is essential that you have experience in the following areas;<br> <ul> <li>Issues management</li> <li>Experience working for a large global organisation&nbsp;</li> <li>Experience working across APAC</li> <li>Experience managing people</li> <li>Understands the complexity of working In Asia for a multi-national company</li> <li>Confident addressing senior management</li> <li>Strong influencing skills</li> </ul> <div>Experience working for an airline would be an advantage.&nbsp;<br> <br> </div> This role will involve extensive travel and some irregular working&nbsp;hours.<br> <br> <strong>Singapore based<br> </strong> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel: Katie-Jo Green -&nbsp;R1441403<br> </em><em> </em><em> </em><em></em><em></em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Communications, PR, Regional, Singapore, Corporate Communications</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636751" id="4278">Corporate Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2043738" reference="2067324" datePosted="2015-07-20" dateUpdated="2015-07-19T19:40:32Z">
    <Title>Senior Account Executive - Financial PR</Title>
    <Summary>Global PR agency are expending their Singapore office and require the support of a Senior Account Executive.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> A global PR agency specialise in PR, Public Relations, Investor Relations and Financial communications. This Dynamic business who are primarily finance focussed work strategically to enable businesses to achieve their business goals.&nbsp;<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> Aside from supporting the senior team and day to day account handling and execution with direction from senior team, your responsibilities will include,&nbsp;News monitoring &amp; press summaries.<br> You will research for current clients and new business opportunities; assists with the preparation of materials such as presentations, press releases, key messages, Q&amp;As, biographies, press kits and&nbsp;Provide general logistical support<br> <br> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;<br> </strong>This PR agency are looking for 2-5 years of PR experience, either in house or agency. &nbsp;You must have a strong academic record, a strong understanding of&nbsp;business environment and current affairs and have excellent&nbsp;written and oral communication skills.<br> It i essential that you have strong relationship skills and to command the confidence of others both internally and externally as well as financial literacy and knowledge of capital markets and financial industry.]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Finance, Financial, PR, Public Relations, Communications, Comms, IR, Investor</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636767" id="4294">PR - Account Executive</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2044195" reference="2055417" datePosted="2015-07-20" dateUpdated="2015-07-19T22:45:48Z">
    <Title>Digital Project Manager</Title>
    <Summary>Our client is a new leading technology and creative company with 10 offices around the world working with top notch clients in the consumer sector.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company...<br> <br> </strong>Our client is a new leading technology and creative company with 10 offices around the world working with top notch clients in the consumer sector.<br> <br> <strong>The Role...<br> <br> </strong>As a Digital Project Manager, you will be responsible for ensuring the consistent and timely delivery of our creative and innovative campaigns.&nbsp;<strong><br> </strong><br> <strong>Responsibilities...</strong>&nbsp;<br> <ul> <li> You will take campaign briefs from client services teams and work with all of our internal production functions including design and development teams to craft exciting mobile experiences.</li> <li> This role requires an approachable and communicative person who can work closely with a variety of internal functions to ensure campaigns are scoped correctly and the right requirements are met.</li> <li> You will then have to liaise continuously with our delivery teams ensuring that all design and technical details are followed precisely and delivered on time.&nbsp;</li> </ul> <strong>&amp; You..</strong><br> <ul> <li>3 years of campaign and project management experience (Ideally in creative/digital advertising)</li> <li>Commercial acumen and a deep understanding of trafficking creative and advertising workflows</li> <li>Excellent internal stake-holder management skills with exposure to managing multiple campaigns simultaneously</li> <li>A strong problem solving ability and a creative mindset</li> <li>Fluency in English is required to be successful in this international environment</li> </ul> <strong>To apply:</strong> please use the application buttons below, or e-mail your CV in Words format to kay@jobadder.com<br> <br> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and numerous other corporate, agency and network clients. &nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to hello@jobadder.com &nbsp;We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;<br> </em><em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel:&nbsp;Kay Lee Meng Qi -&nbsp;R1546136</em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Digital Project Manager, Project Manager - Digital Marketing</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636741" id="4269">Digital Media</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2044262" reference="2088022" datePosted="2015-07-20" dateUpdated="2015-07-20T00:53:37Z">
    <Title>Head of Corporate Communications for SEA &amp; ANZ</Title>
    <Summary>A global brand producing household brands are seeking a Head of Corporate Communications to continue developing markets across APAC.</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong>The Company</strong><br> <br> With a head quarters based in Europe, this company are globally leading market positions both in the consumer and industrial sector today and are known for many household brands. This company are continuing to grow their strong presence emerging markets across Asia.<br> <br> <strong>The Role</strong><br> <ul> <li>Develop and implement an annual corporate communications plan and strategy in Southeast Asia, Australia &amp; New Zealand, covering external and internal communications in line with the Global Corporate Communications strategic priorities as well as the country strategy and in close alignment with the Regional Head</li> <li>Monitor consistently and ensure progress against the objectives to guide the development of an annual corporate communications plan in key countries</li> <li>Ensure standard approach for non-key countries and take responsibility for crisis and issues management in non-key countries as mandatory member of the local crisis management team</li> <li>Manage&nbsp;the&nbsp;team&nbsp;of Corporate Communications and cooperate with region and global headquarters to ensure proper information flow as well as exchange or roll-out of best practices</li> <li>Continuously enhance the standards and levels of&nbsp;Corporate Communications &nbsp;within the region by&nbsp;pro-actively&nbsp;sharing best practices</li> </ul> <strong>&amp; You...&nbsp;</strong> <ul> <li>Minimum of 9 years' experience acquired in Corporate Communications</li> <li>Minimum 3 years of leadership experience</li> <li>Good knowledge of local media and political landscape in the region with established contacts to the local media</li> <li>Flexible to travel within the region of responsibility</li> </ul> <strong>33 Talent</strong><br> <em>33 Talent specialises in Big Data, Digital and Communications recruitment and talent management&nbsp;across the APAC region. &nbsp;Our clients include Lenovo, AMEX, SingTel, The Body Shop, Amobee, SAP, WPP Group, McCann Worldgroup, IPG and&nbsp;numerous other corporate, agency and network clients.&nbsp;&nbsp; Please get in touch or feel free to make referrals to&nbsp;hello@jobadder.com&nbsp; We'd love to hear from you!&nbsp;<br> </em><br> <em>33 Talent Singapore Private Limited</em><br> <em>EA License Number 13C6298<br> </em><em>EA Personnel: Katie-Jo Green -&nbsp;R1441403<br> </em><em></em><em></em><em> </em><em></em><em></em>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Corporate, communications, FMCG, Manager, APAC, regional, consumer</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636092" id="528">Communications</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636772" id="4299">PR Manager</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636164" id="14">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636800" id="30">Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816807" id="150">All Singapore</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
  <Job jid="2045616" reference="1782059" datePosted="2015-07-21" dateUpdated="2015-07-20T23:00:12Z">
    <Title>Group Sales Manager</Title>
    <Summary>Global Mobile Tech company searching for a Group Sales Manager to work in either they Sydney or Melbourne office</Summary>
    <Description><![CDATA[<strong></strong><strong>The Company:&nbsp;</strong>A Global Mobile Technology company who are leading the way in mobile user experience and engagement.Through&nbsp;building and owning their own industry first platforms this are market leaders and experts in their space.&nbsp;They are a dynamic young team with a fun work hard / play hard culture and very cool offices in Sydney<br> <strong><br> The Role:</strong><br> <ul> <li>Will see you lead, support and develop a team of Sales Account Managers with day-to-day business activities, &amp; senior client interaction&nbsp;</li> <li>Will see you oversee facilitate new business pitches within your team and be the key spokesperson with senior stakeholders</li> <li>Will see you identify emerging verticals and develop sales strategies and tactics that capitalise on market changes and opportunities</li> <li>Will see you cultivate relationships with clients and help your team members to gain a deeper insight into their business in order to provide expert solutions to their business goals</li> </ul> <strong>You...</strong>&nbsp;<br> <ul> <li>Will have extensive digital/mobile sales and strategy experience</li> <li>Will have strong team management and leadership experience</li> <li>Will be a straight shooter who is confident, assertive and able to take ownership of a major business account</li> <li>Will have a strong understanding of Display, RTB, Search, SMS, Rich Media and App Downloads&nbsp;</li> <li>Will have first rate communication skills and proven experience delivering against client objectives</li> <li>Will have a strong passion for mobile and technology</li> </ul>]]></Description>
    <SearchTitle>Global Mobile Tech Group Sales Manager</SearchTitle>
    <Classifications>
      <Classification jid="15365" name="Job Category" vid="636088" id="527">Digital</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15366" name="Sub-Category" vid="636745" id="4273">Mobile</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15405" name="Country" vid="636163" id="1">Australia</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15410" name="Location" vid="636785" id="1">Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="16810" name="Area" vid="816806" id="1">All Sydney</Classification>
      <Classification jid="15368" name="Work Type" vid="636197" id="2">Full Time</Classification>
    </Classifications>
    <Fields />
  </Job>
</Jobs>